Sabastian Storm White Belser, MBA

sswbelser.com sswbelser@gmail.com (510) 847-6982 linkedin.com/in/sswbelser github.com/sswbelser @sswbelser

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I have worked several years in human resources and operations. I have a proven HR track record as a generalist, HRIS specialist, and recruiter, I have managed teams of over 30 employees, I am a fast learner with high charisma, and I am a hobbyist software/game developer. My education and unique work experiences make me a great fit for a company seeking an HR professional who speaks the language of developers.

EDUCATION

2015

General Assembly, San Francisco Web Development Immersive

2014

Golden Gate University, San Francisco
MBA: Management / Information Systems

2012

University of California, Davis BA: Sociology / Organizational Studies

SKILLS

HRMS/ ATS Administration		Business Analytics
•	Taleo	Full-Cycle Recruiting
•	ADP	Benefits Administration
•	PeopleSoft	Interviews/Onboarding
•	Workday	Workers' Compensation
•	Newton	Business Analytics
•	SalesForce	Operations Management
•	Various legacy systems	Software/Game Development

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly

Front End Development TA | 2015-Current

- Assisting head instructor with teaching various front end languages, frameworks, and libraries
- Leading discussion groups/stand-ups on specific topics
- Offering one-on-one mentorship to students as needed
- While I was an immersive student, I was asked to represent the school in front of representatives from the governor's office and the <u>Wall Street Journal</u>

GHD Inc.

Human Resources Generalist | 2014-2015

- HRIS & ATS: PeopleSoft, ADP, Taleo, e-learning, and legacy systems
- Administered e-learning systems
- · Facilitated new hire orientations
- Managed the onboarding and offboarding processes
- Resolved staff conflicts/inquiries
- · Process analyses and consolidation for company merger

Bauer's Intelligent Transportation

Account Manager | 2013-2014

- Managed operations of the UC Berkeley bus system
- · Project management to increase operational efficiency

Berkshire Hathaway Homestate Companies

Human Resources Assistant | 2012-2013

- HRIS & ATS: ADP, SharedHR, Workday, and legacy systems
- Recruited various technical and non-technical positions including the company's new CIO - for various offices across the country
- Conducted applicant phone screens and assessment tests
- Administrated benefits through various vendors
- Managed the onboarding and offboarding processes
- · Facilitated new hire orientations
- Training upper management on systems/functionalities
- Hired, trained, and supervised the internship program

Specialized Transportation Services/Tipsy Taxi

Director | 2009-2012

- Hired, trained, and mentored ~30 direct reports
- Responsible for all operations and finances
- Rolled out sweeping operations and administrative changes, which resulted in much a higher revenue
- Worked with various government bodies on grants for large capital purchases

Unitrans

Planning Manager / Outreach & Retention Coordinator | 2008-2012

- After starting as a bus driver, I held various part time leadership and management roles at Unitrans
- Supervised ~15 office clerks and planning assistants
- Managed and resolved all customer complaints
- Assisted in implementing new NextBus tracking system both customer-facing and internal functionalities
- Recruited all student positions sourced resumes, scheduled/conducted interviews, etc.